Hello everyone. You are listening to Enjoy Simple English. 森崎ウィンです。
毎週木曜日は、Winston from the West. 2019年度に放送した古典が語る西洋の知恵をお送りいたします。
今日お送りするのは、あの有名なThe Rabbit and the Turtle. ウサギとカメです。早速聞いてみましょう。
It was a beautiful day in the mountains.
The wind blew gently,
and the sun shone through the leaves in the trees.
All the animals on the mountain
were enjoying the afternoon together quietly.
Then, a rabbit started to talk.
Let's do something!
Oh, I know!
Let's see who can run the fastest!
That sounds like a good idea.
Turtle, do you want to race with me?
Yes, it sounds like fun.
Ha ha ha, but you are so slow.
You have such short legs and a heavy shell on your back.
How are you going to run?
I don't have to run to win a race.
What are you talking about?
Don't you know that I can run fast like the wind?
I know you are fast, but I will win.
Will you race with me?
Or are you afraid to lose against the turtle?
Ha ha ha! This is really funny!
But if you want to lose, I will race with you!
そこで フォックスが 始まり 目的地 目的地 目的地を 選んでくれました
その日 ラビットとトルトルは 始まり線に立ち
フォックスが 試合を 始めるのを 待ちました
全ての動物は その周りに 立ち上がって 笑顔をしていました
レディー セット ゴー!
ラビットは 風が速く 飛び出しました
and the turtle started walking at his usual speed
The rabbit ran and ran until he was far ahead of the turtle
He stopped for a moment
Hahaha! The turtle is so slow!
I know I will win this race!
He can never catch me now!
Oh!
What a beautiful day!
The grass is so soft here
I think I will rest for a while
Then I will run to the goal
So the rabbit lay down on the grass
and closed his eyes
He didn't plan to stay long
But the gentle sunshine and the wind felt good
and he became sleepy
In a few minutes
ラベットは寝ていた
ラベットが寝ていたら
トルトルは歩き続けた
一度も止まらなかった
歩いて歩いて
ゴールに近づいていた
ラベットは起きて
ああ、いい感じだ!
今、また走り始める準備ができた!
レッツ シー ウェア イズ ザ スロー トゥ トゥ トゥ ウォッ オー ノー
この物語はもう小さい頃から聞かされた物語ですね
僕の今台本にあなたはどっちですかって書いてあるんですけれども
僕は多分うさぎです
地道にコツコツやること大事ですね
それではSee you tomorrow